声明: 本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
欢迎访问官方论坛  www.YYeTs.net 在线观看 剧情讨论 学习交流
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：Requiem校对扣扣
后期：阿胜 双语制作：sealovemoon
========== 字幕总监制：七色九天 ==========
你为什么想娶我女儿?
Paik先生
我虽是来自一个小渔村但是有我的理想和追求
那你的雄心大志是什么?
开一家酒店
为的是有一天能拥有自己的酒店
你父亲是怎么看待这桩婚事的?
我父亲?
他去世了
那你都能为我女儿做什么呢?
任何事情
即使是替我做事?
当然
我为什么要把女儿嫁给一个轻易就出卖自己理想的男人呢?
因为
她就是我的梦想
先生
你到底在做什么?
你是不是脑子有问题?
他们又开始了
There they go again.
你说我们是不是该做点什么?
You think we should do something?
我们能做什么呢?
What should we do?
发生什么事了?
What's going on?
我不知道 他走过去 然后就开始纠缠不清
I don't know. He walked up and started going off on her again.
把你的手放开!
Get your hands off her!
我发誓你再敢碰她一下
I swear to God, you put your hands on her one more time...
把你的手拿开!
Get your hands off me!
你和他之间发生过什么?
和谁?
Michael
太可笑了
是吗?
什么也没有
这颜色真漂亮
非常漂亮
你一定很高兴结婚吧
我能和我老婆单独呆一会儿吗?
千万别忘了楼下还有你们的客人
我好开心
真希望你的父亲能目睹这一切
对不起  我使你不高兴了
没有
不管他在那里 我想他都会以我为荣的
能帮我拉上吗?
一定要吗?
咱们什么时候去度蜜月?
Sun...
你知道我想去 只是现在...
我只想让你父亲看到我是尽职尽责的.
他不会拿这个来为难你的 更何况  我是他的女儿
给我6个月...
等我的管理培训全部都结束了
难道我还没有他的汽车公司重要吗?
我保证...
我们会有一个我们梦想已久的蜜月的...
Michael
对不起
I'm sorry.
没关系
Don't worry.
是我自己多管闲事
I stuck my nose where it didn't belong.
我自找的
It's on me.
你必须知道
You must understand.
我必须把这个竹筏做好
I got to get this raft finished
那样我就能带我儿子离开这里回家
so I can get my boy and take him home.
当我打你的时候
When I slapped you,
我是在保护你
I was protecting you.
-是吗?  保护我什么?  -避开Jin.
-Yeah? From what?  -From Jin.
你不知道他会做出什么样的事情
You don't know what he's capable of.
那不关我事
It's not my problem.
是你的问题
It's yours.
你为什么不试试海胆?
Why don't you try sea urchin?
他们的砰砰声更大
They got more ping.
听着 我知道在海滩上发生了不愉快的事情
So listen,I know things got kind of nasty down there at the beach.
我不想被牵连到你们的家事里 但是
I don't want to get involved in husband and wife stuff,but
我认为 你看
I figured, you know,
你也许需要放松
you might need to relax.
所以...
So...
来吧 伙计 我好言相劝
Come on, dude, I'm trying here.
好吧
OK.
你不想加入?
You want to be an outsider?
那是你的事
It's your business.
我把这边绑紧
I tied this side down.
你认为这个撑得住吗?
Do you think this is gonna hold?
你是不是在海军服过役而你却忘记告诉我了?
Do you have a past in the Navy you've neglected to tell me about?
为什么这么说?
Why?
像你这样的一个女人 怎么能打出这样完美的结呢?
How does a woman like you learn how to tie a perfect bowline knot?
跟一些玩帆船的人约会喽
By dating guys with sailboats.
既然你提到了 第一次遇见你的时候 我还担心
Since you bring it up, I've been worried since I first met you
你这辈子会嫁不出去呢
that you might end up a spinster.
然后星期六晚上待在家里绑绳节?
Spending my Saturday nightsalone at home tying knots?
或许还有一位超重的姑妈
Perhaps with an overweight aunt.
真是个伤心的画面
It's a very sad image.
或许我们得拿些绳子
Maybe we should get some rope,
在一个周六整晚呆在一起
spend a Saturday night alone together,
看看会发生什么
and see what happens.
爸
Dad?
谢了
Thanks.
你会喜欢上纽约的 Walt
You are going to love New York, Walt.
没有哪个城市能比她好
No city like it.
到了纽约我最想给你看的是
What I really want to show you
那些高楼 建筑
Are the buildings, architecture.
高楼?
Buildings?
对 我过去也认为没什么 直到我见到了熨斗形大厦
I said that,'til I saw the Flatiron Building.
城市里古老的摩天大楼
Oldest skyscraper in the city.
建于1902年 而且是扁平的
Built in 1902.And it's flat.
那个建筑给了我画画还有
That one building inspired me to start drawing
设计东西的灵感
and designing things.
你看到就知道了 想马上就看到 对吧?
You just gotta see it.You want to see it, right?
我想是吧
I guess.
我去和 Vincent玩会球可以吗?
Can I go throw the ball to Vincent?
好的  当然行了
Yeah. Sure. Of course.
快 Vincent!
Come on, Vincent!
哇噢  进展不错啊
Wow, you're making a lot of progress.
-是啊 挺麻烦的  -挺棒的
-Yeah, trying.  -It's pretty cool.
用这些竹子做甲板
Got this bamboo for the decking,
用机身做船舱
got a piece of the fuselage for a cabin
一些储藏箱
Some storage bins.
我想给你提点醒
I thought I'd give you the heads-up.
是吗?
Yeah?
对 大家都在谈论谁会跟你一起走
Yeah, there's a lot of talk going on about who's going on this thing with you.
老兄...这可不是"玛丽皇后"号
Hey, man... it's not the Queen Mary.
只能容纳4个人
I only got room for four people.
还剩下一个空位
There's one open spot.
另外一个给谁了?
Who took the other one?
你怎么了,医生?
What's the matter, doc?
感觉被冷落了?
Feeling left out?
你准备带Sawyer一起走?
You're taking Sawyer with you?
没错 我给自己买了张船票
Yep. Bought myself a ticket on this little tub.
告诉你吧
Let me tell you.
票价还挺贵的
The fare was steep.
本来还可以用这些电缆撑住我的沙滩别墅的整个东翼的
Could have used that cable to hold up the whole east wing of my new beach house.
你卖给他一个位置?
You sold him a spot?
因为我需要给桅杆找条扬帆索
I needed a halyard to the mast.
还好我是个节俭的人 不会浪费钱财 对吧 医生?
Good thing I'm a saver, not a spender, huh, doc?
你还想让你丈夫这样对待你多久?
How much longer are you gonna let him treat you this way?
拜托...
Please
Sun
他是我的丈夫
He's my husband.
是啊,一个连你会说英语都不敢告诉他知道的丈夫?
Yeah, a husband you're afraid to tell you speak English
我在试着去理解  Sun
I'm trying to understand, Sun.
他以前不是这样的
He wasn't always like this.
他过去常常跟我说我有多漂亮
He used to tell me how beautiful I looked to him.
他以前很温柔
He was so tender.
后来他变了
And then he was different.
什么改变了他?
What changed him?
快来帮忙!
Need some help!
Charlie  出什么事了?
Hey, Charlie, what's going on?
那船...着火了 看!
The raft…it's on fire. Look.
不!
No!
他在哪里?
Where is he?
他到底在哪里?
Where the hell is he?!
他在哪里?
Where is he?
她听不懂你的话 老兄
She doesn't understand you, man.
他在哪里?
Hey! Where is he?
走开
Back off.
不 是她丈夫干的 她知道的!
No. Her husband did this, and she knows!
你现在想保护他是吗?
You trying to protect him now? Is that it?
她刚才跟我在一起!
She was with me!
Walt! 不要 Walt! 回来 回来
Walt! No, Walt! Get back, get back.
不 不要 没用了
No, no, it's done.
Sun 等等!
Sun, wait!
我非打死他不可!
I'm gonna break his damn neck!
Michael 先别生气
Michael, just take it easy, man.
我们并不能确定是Jin干的
We don't know that Jin did this.
-你开玩笑吗?  -Sawyer 闭嘴!
-Are you serious?!  -Sawyer, shut up!
Jack  别这样  早上我们看见他在这沙滩上
Jack, come on, we saw him on the beach this morning!
那并不意味着就是他烧了这船
That doesn't mean that he torched the raft.
那是谁干的 Jack?
Yeah, then who did, Jack?
Jin
你在干什么?
What do you want?
我受伤了
是你干的?
Michael这么尽力帮咱们离开这个岛...
你为什么要...
Michael?
对于所发生的事 我负全部责任
那机器老化了  我本应该...
我叫你来不是为了训斥你
而是提升你
你将成为我的新任特别助理
先生...
我不知道要...
你知道 Byung Han吧?
环境安全公司的部长?
今晚到他家里替我传递个信息
就说我非常不高兴
你是谁?
我叫Jin-Soo Kwon
有什么事?
我替Paik先生做事的
Kwon先生...请进
请
请坐
喝点东西好吗?
不用 谢了
我过来传个信息
请...不要在我女儿面前...
Paik先生对你很生气
就这样
谢谢你
谢谢!
真的很感谢
请告诉Paik先生我不会再让他生气了...
如果有什么机会让我表示一下歉意...
小小意思
这是冠军品种
韩部长
很值钱的 请告诉Paik先生我很抱歉
你能帮说一下吗?
我不能...
请你一定要
谢谢 谢谢!
有什么事?
What do you want?
我想跟你谈谈 Shannon
I'd like to talk to you about Shannon.
你妹妹跟我很可能会不只是朋友
It's very possible your sister and I are going to become more than just friends.
这算什么  中东人的方式?
What is this, some middle eastern thing?
你要我的祝福还是什么?
You want my blessing or something?
我希望你不会反对
My hope is you won't object.
我只是想礼貌些  而不是来请求你的准许
I was extending a courtesy, not asking your permission.
跟你说说我妹妹吧
Let me tell you about my sister.
他喜欢成熟的男人...那种可以照顾她的
She likes older men...guys that can take car eof her.
我猜在这里你刚好符合这个条件
My guess is in this place you fit the bill.
她会让你觉得自己是最好的
She'll make you feel like the greatest guy ever while you
然后你给她弄食物 一切她要的东西
get her food,whatever it is she needs,
在得到她所需要的之后
and once she gets what she wants,
她就会离开你
she'll move on.
如果到时她真的离开你
When she does,
别太在意
don't take it personally, man.
你把我的船搞砸了 老大
Messed up my ride, chief.
原来你在这
Hey, there you are.
过来帮下忙 我快把它弄坏了
Come help me with this. I'm completely destroying it.
看起来弄得不错啊
You seem to be doing just fine.
是吗 好到差不多倒掉了
Yeah, fine at making it collapse.
其实你很能干 Shannon
You're very capable, Shannon.
我相信你能亲自搞定它
I'm sure you'd be all right building it on your own.
你怎么了?
What's going on?
或许你该另外找个朋友来帮你搞定你的棚子
Perhaps you should find another friend to help you with your shelter.
你告诉我哥了 对吧?
You've been talking to my brother, haven't you?
真恶心!
Oh, gross!
对你来说是恶心 对我可是晚餐
Gross to you, dinner to me.
Boone在哪里?
Boone  where is he?
不知道
Don't know.
你什么意思  你不知道?你们两个简直像丛林兄弟
What do you mean, you don't know? You two are like jungle pals.
不好意思 我没见过他
Sorry. I haven't seen him.
那 如果你见到他
Well, if you do see him,
告诉他闭上他的臭嘴 如果他有什么话要说
tell him to keep his stupid mouth shut, and if he has something to say,
当面跟我说 不要把Sayid搅进来
he can leave Sayid out of it and come say it to my face.
我是否应该把它写下来?
Should I be writing this down?
告诉他不要管我的闲事
Just…just tell him to stay the hell out of my business.
你喜欢他吗?
Do you like him?
什么?
What?
Sayid
你是在开玩笑吗?
Are you serious?
因为如果你确实喜欢他
Because if you do like him,
那跟你哥有什么关系?
what's it got to do with your brother?
你是个成年人了
You're a grown woman.
当然 你可以继续对Boone吼到脖子粗
Sure, you can yell at Boone till you're blue in the face,
但你所做的一切正是他想要的
but all you're doing is giving him what he wants.
是吗  他想要什么?
Yeah, what's that?
你的注意
Your attention.
每个人都在这岛上获得了一次新生 Shannon
Everyone gets a new life on this island, Shannon.
也许是时候开始你自己的了
Maybe it's time you start yours.
你肯定很害怕了 对吧?
You must be pretty scared, huh?
害怕  你知道什么是害怕  是吧?
Scared. You understand scared, don't you?
是不是?
Huh?
等下你就知道什么叫害怕了  Bruce
If you ain't, you're gonna be, Bruce.
一个月前沙滩上或许是医生跟会计师而已
Folks down on the beach might have been doctors and accountants a month ago,
但现在是《苍蝇王》时间了
but it's "lord of the flies" time now.
继续走
停
转过来
坐下
好丰盛啊!
这些都是你做的?
为你做的 我想我们一起好好享受一顿
我很高兴你能做这些
别担心
今晚不工作
谢谢
没事
尝尝这个
为什么把我的工厂给关闭了?
因为你没传递好这个简单的信息 我即将损失几百万你知道吗?!
今晚你跟我的同事去Byung Han家
他会告诉你什么是真正的传达信息
等会不要熄火
我会在两分钟内出来
我回来的时候 你不要开超速了
然后把车开到八公里外的河堤
明白吗?
快跑!快!
Kwon先生...等等 让我解释
明天把工厂开了
我刚刚救了你的命
他知道该怎么做了
拜托你说句话
你受伤了?
这是谁的血?
你刚才去干什么了?
到底发生什么事了?
我去做事了
做什么事?
你替我爸做什么事?
看着我
回答我
我做任何你爸要我做的事
为了我们而做
Michael! 有话好好说!
Michael! Take it easy!
好好说,好啊!
I'll take it easy, all right!
别急 老兄
Hang on, man!
你这家伙烧了我的船?
Hey, man, you burned my raft?
冷静一下
Just calm down.
你让开!冷静一下
Hey, step aside, man! Just calm down!
你敢烧我的船?你干嘛烧我的船?
You burned my raft? Why'd you burn my raft, man?
冷静一下 想清楚了
Calm down and think about it for a minute.
看看他的手  老兄
Look at his hands, man.
走开啦 Jack  这事跟你无关
Back off, Jack. It's got nothing to do with you.
闭嘴! 大家都冷静一下!
Shut it! Everyone's gotta chill out!
他说了什么?
What'd he say?
你在跟我说话?
You say something to me?
Michael!
再说一次
Say it again.
不 不 不 你再说一次!
No, no, no, say it again, man!
Michael!
放松点 医生
Hey, easy, doc!
一次一场
One fight at a time.
他说的对 这是他们两的事
He's right. This is between them.
住手!
Stop it!
放开他!
Leave him alone!
他没有烧你的船
He didn't burn your raft.
你会说英语?
You speak english?
真没有想到
Didn't see that coming.
你能听懂我们的话?
You understood us
一直以来? 为什么你什么都不说?
all this time?Why didn't you say anything?
当他到的时候你的船已经着火了
Your raft was already on fire when he arrived.
他为了灭火把手给烧伤了
He burned his hands trying to put it out.
那他为什么还要跑掉?
Then why did he run?
没说错吧 和我想的一样
Exactly. That's what I thought.
说我先生什么都行
My husband is many things,
但他绝不是个说谎的人
but he is not a liar.
你还想跟我们谈撒谎?
You're gonna lecture us about lying, Betty?
从他的表情看来
From the look on his face,
即使是你丈夫都不知道你会说英语
even your old man here didn't know you speak English.
我们又怎么知道她是不是包庇他
How do we know she's not covering for him?
因为她没有!
Because she isn't!
他为什么要烧那船?
Why would he burn the raft?
他从第一天开始就缠着我! 人人都知道!
He's been after me since day one! Everybody knows it!
好吧 那是私人恩怨
Okay, it's personal.
但他为什么要放弃我们离开这岛的最好机会?
Why would any one of us block an attempt
我们谁会自断回家的路呢?
to get home?
我们急切地把矛头指向对方
We're so intent on pointing the finger at one another
却忽略了一个简单而不可否认的事实
that we're ignoring the simple undeniable truth
那就是问题根本不在这里!在那里!
that the problem isn't here, it's there!
他们袭击我们
They've attacked us!
破坏我们  绑架我们  谋杀我们
Sabotaged us, abducted us, murdered us.
或许是时候停止相互责备了
Maybe it's time we stop blaming us
担心一下他们吧!
and started worrying about them!
这个岛上并不只有我们 大家都知道!
We're not the only people on this island, and we all know it!
他没有做过
He did not do it.
看看这
Look at this.
一点可用的东西都没有
I can't salvage a thing.
浮筒 甲板...
Pontoons, the decking...
全部麻绳都给火烧了!
fire burnt up all the twine!
该死的!
Damn it!
该死!
老天...
God...
对不起 孩子
I'm sorry, man.
不
No.
过来
Come here.
听着...
Look...
人人都会遇到挫折
we all have setbacks.
我是说 上天知道的
I mean, god knows, man.
这就是生活
That's just life.
我们重新来过  好吗?
We'll start over, all right?
你要再建一艘?
You're gonna build another one?
一艘更好的
A better one.
我能帮忙吗?
Can I help?
你当然可以帮忙啦
No doubt you can help.
你在干吗?
回答我
你想去哪里...
去沙滩?
你决定就这样对我是吗?
为什么不告诉我你没有烧那船?
你倒是说话啊  Jin
我究竟做了什么你要这样对我?
我们什么时候开始这样不说话了?
我当时打算离开你的!
I was going to leave you!
我当时真想一走了之
I was going to get away.
但你让我改变了注意
But you made me change my mind.
你让我相信你还爱着我
You made me think that you still loved me.
我想回到从前
我们能不能...
重新开始?
对不起 爸爸
请原谅我
我曾经...
...以你为耻
她人长什么样的?
很漂亮
聪明
冷静
我们俩互不说话了
这是为什么?
因为我不能告诉她...
...关于她爸爸的事
在一个现实的世界里
她会讨厌他的  而不是我
这是个现实的世界
你不知道我干了什么
你是我儿子
你做了什么都没关系
我真希望可以重来
为什么不行?
我有一些职责在身
比你妻子更重要?
他爸爸要我把手表送到他在 悉尼跟洛杉矶的合伙人那里
就算是为他所做的最后一件事吧
...然后离开
不再回来
到美国去
挽救你的婚姻
太迟了
那代表什么?
What was that for?
每个人都在这岛上获得一次新生
Everyone gets a new life on this island.
我想从现在开始
I'd like to start now.
给自己找了个对手?
Got yourself an opponent?
Hurley 欠我83,000美元
Hurley owes me $83,000.
我跟他说我会给他一次机会赢回去的
I told him I'd give him a chance to win it back.
我很久没有跟你玩过了
It's been a while since you and I played.
但我可没有83,000美元
I don't have $83,000.
没关系
That's okay.
你爸呢?
Where's your pop?
我想在沙滩那边
Down at the beach, I think.
天黑后他不准我离开山洞
I'm not allowed to leave the caves after dark.
你有爸爸吗?
Do you have a dad?
人人都有爸爸
Everyone's got a dad.
他酷吗?
Is he cool?
不
No.
不,他不酷
No, he's not.
好!
Yes!
不错
Good for you.
可以问你点事情吗?
Hey, you mind if I ask you something?
当然
Sure.
你为什么烧了那船  Walt?
Why did you burn the raft, Walt?
别担心  我不会告诉别人的
Don't worry. I'm not gonna tell.
你肯定是有很好的理由的
You must have had a really good reason.
我不想再换地方了
I don't want to move anymore.
我长到现在老是在搬家
I've been moving places my whole life.
我喜欢这里
I like it here.
我也喜欢这里
I like it here, too.
船
Boat.
背景音乐是Damien Rice的歌曲  名字是 Delicate
该死的
Son of a bitch.
==============| YYeTs字幕组招募启示  |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国)  双语字幕校正   时间轴调整
英语翻译   欧美影视新闻翻译  影视评论  论坛版主  美工人员
服务器提供者  发布宣传  联系地址：www.YYeTs.com
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报 ====